A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1 FA429
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal Correspondence, 3
  - Bosworth, Francis, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 310)
  - Calenders, Pocket, 1981-1984 (Box 42)
  - Calenders, Pocket, 1985-1988 (Box 43)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1986 Jan.-April (Box 44, Folder 311)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1986 Apil-Dec. (Box 44, Folder 312)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1986 Oct.-Nov. (Box 44, Folder 313)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1986 December 1-8 (Box 44, Folder 314)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1986 December 8-10 (Box 44, Folder 315)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1986 December 12-30 (Box 45, Folder 316)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1987 Jan. (Box 45, Folder 317)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1987 Jan.-Sept. (Box 45, Folder 318)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1987 July-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 319)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1987 April-Nov. (Box 46, Folder 320)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1987 Dec. (Box 46, Folder 321)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 322)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1988 Jan.-March (Box 46, Folder 323)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1988 March-April (Box 46, Folder 324)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 46, Folder 325)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1992 Jan.-March (Box 47, Folder 326)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1992 Feb.-Sept. (Box 47, Folder 327)
  - Oliver Cope, 1979-1981 (Box 47, Folder 328)
  - Oliver Cope, 1981-1983, 1988, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 329)
  - Doris Schwartz Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 330)
  - Expenses, 1981-1983 (Box 47, Folder 331)
  - Family - Father's Side, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 332)
  - Family - Mother's Side, 1928, 1940, 1965, 1972, 1978, 1985-1988 (Box 47, Folder 333)
  - Thelma Ingles, 1972-1977 (Box 48, Folder 334)
  - Thelma Ingles, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 335)
  - Thelma Ingles, 1980-1984, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 336)
  - Insurance - Insurance - Alderman Glick, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 337)
  - Insurance - Aldeman Glick, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 337A)
  - Insurance - Information, 1976, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 338)
  - Insurance - Information, 1976, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 338A)
    Closed from Scholarly Access.
  - Insurance - Insurance Other, 1981 Jan. 29 (Box 48, Folder 339)
  - Insurance - Medical Claims, 1975-1980 (Box 48, Folder 340)
  - Insurance - Medical Claims, 1975-1980 (Box 56, Folder 340A)
  - Insurance - Prudential - RWJF, Insurance - Life and Health, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 341)
  - Insurance - Prudential - RWJF, Insurance - Life and Health li, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 341A)
  - Ms. Eppie Lederer, 1973-1985 (Box 48, Folder 342)
  - L.N.S. Mahoney Award Recipients, 1988-1993 (Box 48, Folder 343)
  - L.N.S. Mahoney Award Reipients, 1987-1989 (Box 56, Folder 343A)
  - Harvey Picker, 1986-1994 (Box 48, Folder 344)
  - Photographs, 1984-1986 (Box 49, Folder 345)
  - Photographs, 1928, 1940, 1965, 1972, 1978, 1980-1991 (Box 49, Folder 346)
  - Personal - Photographs, 1984-1986; 2015:FA429:004 (Item 2015:FA429:004)
  - Personal - Photographs, 1928, 1980-1991; 2015:FA429:005 (Item 2015:FA429:005)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1970-1974, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 347)
  - Travel Expense Reports, 1986 Jan.-July (Box 49, Folder 348)
  - Travel Expense Reports, 1986 Jan.-July (Box 56, Folder 348A)
  - Letters and Cards - Colleges, Family, and Friends, 1972-1993 (Box 50)
  - Letters and Cards - Close MEM Friends, 1964-1991 (Box 51)
  - Letters and Cards - Family Relatives, 1972-1991 (Box 52)
  - Letters and Cards - Get Well, 1992 (Box 53)
    Material is restricted from scholarly access.
  - Letters and Cards - Staff Correspondence, 1979-1993 (Box 54)
  - Trips, 1986-1989 (Box 49, Folder 349)
  - Travel Itineraries, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 350)
  - Homer Wadsworth, 1988-1994 (Box 49, Folder 351)
  - Special Formats and Photographic Materials (Box 55)
- Speeches, 1986-1999; 4
  - Spirit of Man - GHAA MPLS, MN - Correspondence, 1986 June 4 (Box 57, Folder 352)
  - Spirit of Man - GHAA MPLS, MN - Draft, 1986 June 4 (Box 57, Folder 353)
  - Spirit of Man - GHAA MPLS, MN - Final, 1986 June 4 (Box 57, Folder 354)
  - Spirit of Man - GHAA MPLS, MN - References, 1986 June 4 (Box 57, Folder 355)
  - MEM Notes from Harvey Book Recept., 1986 Nov. 9 (Box 57, Folder 356)
  - Lutheran Medical Center, 1987 Jan. 30 (Box 57, Folder 357)
  - University of Missouri, Kansas City - The Promise Ahead - Correspondence, 1987 Jan. 29 (Box 57, Folder 358)
  - University of Missouri, Kansas City - The Promise Ahead - Draft, 1987 Jan. 29 (Box 57, Folder 359)
  - University of Missouri, Kansas City - The Promise Ahead - Final, 1987 Jan. 29 (Box 57, Folder 360)
  - College of Physicians and Surgeons - Changing Role of Patient - Correspondence, 1987 Jan. 25 (Box 57, Folder 361)
  - College of Physicians and Surgeons - Changing Role of Patient - Draft, 1987 Jan. 25 (Box 57, Folder 362)
  - College of Physicians and Surgeons - Changing Role of Patient - Final, 1987 Jan. 25 (Box 57, Folder 363)
  - College of Physicians and Surgeons - Changing Role of Patient - Reference, 1987 Jan. 25 (Box 57, Folder 364)
  - The Heller School - Bigel Institute for Health Policy, 1987 May 15 (Box 57, Folder 365)
  - Landmark Conservancy Recertion - MEM Remarks, 1987 Oct. 13 (Box 57, Folder 366)
  - Women in Financial Development, 1987 Oct. 5 (Box 57, Folder 367)
  - Columbia University - Urban America, 1987 Oct. 28-29 (Box 57, Folder 368)
  - Executive Nurse Fellowship Program, 1988 Jan. 11 (Box 58, Folder 369)
  - Yale School of Organization & Management - Variation Medical Care Practice - Correspondence, 1988 Jan. 21 (Box 58, Folder 370)
  - Yale School of Organization & Management - Variation Medical Care Practice - Draft/Final, 1988 Jan. 21 (Box 58, Folder 371)
  - Massachusetts Saving Lives Program - Announcement, 1988 March 30 (Box 58, Folder 372)
  - Kingsport, TN - The Kingsport Partners - Correspondence/References, 1988 May 23 (Box 58, Folder 373)
  - Kingsport, TN - The Kingsport Partners - Draft, 1988 May 23 (Box 58, Folder 374)
  - Frank Thistlethwaite -Dinner, 1999 Jan. 20 (Box 58, Folder 375)
  - Bar Association of the City of NY - Foundations and the Law - Correspondence, 1989 May 2 (Box 58, Folder 376)
  - Bar Association of the City of NY - Foundations and the Law - Final/Draft, 1989 May 2 (Box 58, Folder 377)
  - NY Regional Association of Grantmakers - MEM Remarks, 1989 May 12 (Box 58, Folder 378)
  - Chicago, IL - Living at Home Speech, 1989 May 15 (Box 58, Folder 379)
  - UK Harkness Fellowships - MEM Remarks, 1989 July 20 (Box 58, Folder 380)
  - Executive Nurse Fellowship Program - MSN - MBA Dinner, 1989 Sept. 21 (Box 58, Folder 381)
  - NY Regional Association of Grantmakers - MEM Remarks, 1989 Nov. 9 (Box 58, Folder 382)
  - Coro Foundation Fellows - MEM Remarks, 1990 March 1 (Box 58, Folder 383)
  - The Cosmopolitan Club - MEM Remarks - Drafts, 1990 March 21 (Box 58, Folder 384)
  - The Cosmopolitan Club - MEM Remarks - Final, 1990 March 21 (Box 59, Folder 385)
  - American Philosophical Society - Medical Rights & Public Welfare - Correspondence, 1990 April 21 (Box 59, Folder 386)
  - American Philosophical Society - Medical Rights & Public Welfare - Final Publication, 1990 April 21 (Box 59, Folder 387)
  - American Philosophical Society - Medical Rights & Public Welfare - Final Speech, 1990 April 21 (Box 59, Folder 388)
  - Marymount College Graduation - MEM Speech - Correspondence, 1990 May 20 (Box 59, Folder 389)
  - Marymount College Graduation - MEM Speech - Final/Draft, 1990 May 20 (Box 59, Folder 390)
  - Harkness Fellows 65th Anniversary - MEM Remarks, 1990 July 18 (Box 59, Folder 391)
  - Executive Nurse Fellowship Program - MEM Remarks, 1990 Aug. 9-10 (Box 59, Folder 392)
  - Countee Cullen Branch NY Public Library - MEM Remarks, 1990 Aug. 18 (Box 59, Folder 393)
  - Countee Cullen Branch NY Public Library, 1990 Aug. 18; 2015:FA429:006 (Item 2015:FA429:006)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Convocation Exercise - Notes/Correspondence, 1990 Sept. 18 (Box 59, Folder 394)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Convocation Exercise - Final, 1990 Sept. 18 (Box 59, Folder 395)
  - MEM Comments on Article by Peter Salins - NYC, 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 396)
  - Donors Forum of Ohio - Correspondence, 1990 Ot. 25 (Box 59, Folder 397)
  - Donors Forum of Ohio - MEM Remarks - Final, 1990 Oct. 25 (Box 59, Folder 398)
- 1995 Accession, 1980-1992; 5; 8.8 Cubic Feet
  Scope and Contents
  Primarily contains correspondence, documentation of Board of Directors and Annual Meetings of Corporation, Phone Logs
  - Record of Interviews, 1985-1988 (Box 60, Folder 399)
  - General Correspondence - A-D, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 400)
  - General Correspondence - E-H, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 401)
  - General Correspondence - I-M, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 402)
  - General Correspondence - N-P, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 403)
  - General Correspondence - R-S, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 404)
  - General Correspondence - T-Z, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 405)
  - General Correspondence - A, 1989-1991 (Box 61, Folder 406)
  - General Correspondence - B, 1989-1991 (Box 61, Folder 407)
  - General Correspondence - Business-Higher Education, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 408)
  - General Correspondence - C, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 409)
  - General Correspondence - D, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 410)
  - General Correspondence - D-F, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 411)
  - General Correspondence - H, 1989-1991 (Box 63, Folder 412-413)
  - General Correspondence - I, 1989-1991 (Box 63, Folder 414)
  - General Correspondence - J, 1989-1991 (Box 63, Folder 415)
  - General Correspondence - K, 1989-1991 (Box 63, Folder 416)
  - General Correspondence - L, 1989-1991 (Box 63, Folder 417)
  - General Correspondence - M, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 418)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney - Memoranda, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 419-420)
  - General Correspondence - N, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 421)
  - General Correspondence - O, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 422)
  - General Correspondence - P-Q, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 423)
  - General Correspondence - R, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 424)
  - General Correspondence - S, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 425-426)
  - General Correspondence - T, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 427)
  - General Correspondence - U-V, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 428)
  - General Correspondence - W, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 429)
  - General Correspondence - X-Z, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 430)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1981 July 7 (Box 66, Folder 431)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1982 April 13 (Box 66, Folder 432-433)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1982 July 13 (Box 66, Folder 434-435)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1982 November 9 (Box 66, Folder 436-437)
  - Annual Meeting, 1982 November 9 (Box 66, Folder 438)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 April 12 (Box 67, Folder 439-440)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 July 12 (Box 67, Folder 441-442)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 November 8 (Box 67, Folder 443)
  - Annual Meeting, 1983 November 8 (Box 67, Folder 444)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1984 April 10 (Box 67, Folder 445)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1984 July 10 (Box 67, Folder 446)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1984 November 13 (Box 67, Folder 447)
  - Annual Meeting, 1984 November 13 (Box 67, Folder 448)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1985 April 9 (Box 67, Folder 449)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1985 July 9 (Box 68, Folder 450)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1985 November 12 (Box 68, Folder 451)
  - Annual Meeting, 1985 November 12 (Box 68, Folder 452)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1986 April 8 (Box 68, Folder 453)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1986 July 8 (Box 68, Folder 454)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1986 November 11 (Box 68, Folder 455)
  - Annual Meeting, 1986 November 11 (Box 68, Folder 456)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 April 14 (Box 68, Folder 457)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 July 14 (Box 68, Folder 458)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 November 10 (Box 68, Folder 459)
  - Annual Meeting, 1987 November 10 (Box 68, Folder 460)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 February 9 (Box 68, Folder 461-462)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 April 12 (Box 69, Folder 463)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 July 12 (Box 69, Folder 464)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 November 8 (Box 69, Folder 465)
  - Annual Meeting, 1988 November 8 (Box 69, Folder 466)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 April 11 (Box 69, Folder 467)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 July 11 (Box 69, Folder 468)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 November 11 (Box 69, Folder 469)
  - Annual Meeting, 1989 November 14 (Box 69, Folder 470)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 April 10 (Box 69, Folder 471)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 July 10 (Box 69, Folder 472)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 November 19 (Box 69, Folder 473)
  - Annual Meeting, 1990 November 19 (Box 69, Folder 474)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1991 April 2 (Box 69, Folder 475)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1991 July 9 (Box 70, Folder 476)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1991 November 26 (Box 70, Folder 477)
  - Annual Meeting, 1991 November 26 (Box 70, Folder 478)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1992 April 7 (Box 70, Folder 479)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1992 July 14 (Box 70, Folder 480)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1992 November 10 (Box 70, Folder 481)
  - Annual Meeting, 1992 November 10 (Box 70, Folder 482)
  - Report of the President and Staff to the Directors of the Commonwealth Fund (Board Report), 1980 September 25 (Box 70, Folder 483)
  - Commonwealth Fund Forum, London, 1983 May 23-26 (Box 70, Folder 484-486)
  - Commonwealth Fund Forum, Whitemarsh, Pennsylvania - Medical Care for the Poor: What Can States Do in the 1990s, 1981 August 9-12 (Box 71, Folder 487-488)
  - Commonwealth Fund Forum, Whitemarsh, Pennsylvania - Medical Care for the Poor: What Can States Do in the 1990s, 1981 August 9-12 (Box 78, Folder 541)
  - Briefing Book and Report on Australia and New Zealand Trip, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 489)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, Camden, ME, 1987 July 30-August 1 (Box 71, Folder 490-491)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, Camden, ME - Invited Participants, 1987 July 30-August 1 (Box 72, Folder 492)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, Camden, ME - Planning, 1987 July 30-August 1 (Box 72, Folder 493)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, Camden, ME - Budget and Expenses, 1987 July 30-August 1 (Box 72, Folder 494)
  - Board of Directors Meeting - Overview and Briefing Book, 1988 February 9 (Box 72, Folder 495-496)
  - Essays for 1988 Annual Report (Box 72, Folder 497)
  - Essays for 1988 Annual Report (Box 73, Folder 498-502)
  - Essays for 1988 Annual Report (Box 74, Folder 503)
  - Essays and Papers for Annual Report, 1986-1988 (Box 74, Folder 504-505)
  - Essays and Papers for 1986 Annual Report (Box 74, Folder 506-507)
  - Essays and Papers for 1986 Annual Report (Box 75, Folder 508)
  - 1980 Search Committee for President, 1978-1980 (Box 75, Folder 509)
  - By-Laws Revision - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 510)
  - By-Laws Revision, 1951-1982 (Box 75, Folder 511-513)
  - By-Laws Revision, 1982-1984 (Box 76, Folder 514)
  - Members of the Corporation and Directors Terms, 1981-1983 (Box 76, Folder 515)
  - Commonwealth Fund Mission Statement, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 516)
  - Board Resolutions, 1984-1989 (Box 76, Folder 517)
  - Nominating Committee, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 518)
  - Board of Directors - Conflict of Interest Statements, 1976-1985 (Box 76, Folder 519-520)
    Restricted from scholary access - Personnel
  - Board of Directors - Foundation Survey, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 521)
  - Board of Directors - Liability Insurance, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 522)
  - Board of Directors - Compensation for Directors, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 523)
  - Board of Directors - Retirement and Benefits, 1979-1980 (Box 76, Folder 524)
  - Board of Directors - Matching Grants (Box 76, Folder 525)
  - Nominating Committee, 1976-1986 (Box 76, Folder 526)
  - Correspondence from Irene Hughes (Exectutive Assistant), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 527)
  - Staff Meetings, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 528)
  - Administrative Meetings, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 529)
  - Telephone Logs, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 530-534)
  - Atherton-Widra Dinner, 1991 September 23 (Box 78, Folder 535)
  - CEPLA Meeting-Dinner - Final, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 536)
  - 1991 Annual Report Letters, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 537)
  - Nursing Shortage Letter, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 538)
  - Teenage Mothers Letter, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 539)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 78, Folder 540)
  - Annual Report - Comments, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 542)
  - Correspondence - United Kingdom, 1984-1990 (Box 78, Folder 543)
  - Administrative Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 544)
  - Telephone Logs, 1992 January-July (Box 78, Folder 545-547)
  - Telephone Logs, 1992 August-December (Box 79, Folder 548-549)
  - Administrative Meetings, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 551)
  - Karen Davis Reception, 1992 July 16 (Box 79, Folder 552)
  - General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 553)
  - General Correspondence - A, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 554)
  - General Correspondence - B, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 555)
  - General Correspondence - C, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 556)
  - General Correspondence - D-F, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 557)
  - General Correspondence - G-I, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 558)
  - General Correspondence - J-L, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 559)
  - General Correspondence - M, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 560)
  - General Correspondence - N, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 561)
  - General Correspondence - P, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 562)
  - General Correspondence - R, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 563)
  - General Correspondence - S, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 564)
  - General Correspondence - T-V, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 565)
  - General Correspondence - W, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 566)